There are as many different ways to take of your tattoo as there are tattoos also.
Everybody's got a theory.
The most important thing is just don't pick at it, don't scratch at it, don't sleep on it and get it stuck to your bed, don't let it get stuck to your clothing and don't over do it.
There are things you want to look out for when you're healing a tattoo such as cleaning products like if you're cleaning your bathroom and you just got your sleeve done, you might not want to get bleach all over your arm.
Thing like that can cause adverse reactions however it's not the end of the world either.
Now of it is life threatening or or or horrifying at all.
As far as the actual healing goes there's a lot of products on the market.
We sell a lot of them here at All or Nothing.
It's easy, a little thing of antibacterial soap in your pocket or whatever.
You go to the bathroom; while you're washing your hands go ahead and wash up here too.
Doesn't hurt anything.
As far as Lubriderm or petroleum based products or all these ointments and salves, really the simpler the better.
Less is more.
If you've got a lotion that's heavy in fragrances it's going to burn because it's going to have alcohol in it so it's going to hurt.
You can use but why would you want to?
You don't have to smell good.
You'll be healed in 3 or 4 days so it's not a big deal.
Vaseline Intensive Care, Lubriderm fragrance free of course.
All these products work.
And all of them have a little bit different way of doing it and your artist will give you, actually most states require that your artist gives you written instructions as you leave the studio.
So it might be very different than what you leave with at our studio and each studio probably has their own theory of of how to do that but as long as it's reasonable I say, I say follow that.